[narrator] Previously on Love Island USA...
The Islanders got
their messages from home.
I'm not a big fan of Destiny anymore.
Leo will never be
a brother-in-law of mine.
It looks more or less forced.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
[narrator] Tonight...
two couples...
must be dumped.
[Sarah]
The two couples with the fewest votes
will be dumped from the island tonight.
[narrator] Welcome to Love Island USA.
Grandpa Bergie's comments
and the message from home
shocked the villa.
Be grateful you saw the edited version.
I had to sit through a 30-minute
update on Grandpa's bunions
with pictures!
Well. hey. I'm really happy.
I love your family.
I know your dad is so important to you.
and your grandma. so I'm just like.
"Wow. they see what we have."
-Like. that's so nice.
-[Marco] Mm-hmm.
-I think that was the last test.
-Mm-hmm.
It does suck. um. for Taylor and Bergie
that Granddad said that.
It just depends on how Bergie's
gonna take that.
-And I mean...
-Seems like he's taking it hard so far.
[Marco]
'Cause I know how much he talks about
his grandparents. and going to the lake.
He said couldn't wait
to take Taylor there. So...
I don't want him to get too in his head.
Everybody that is in here
sees a genuine connection with you guys.
Yeah. I'm just like. "What's fake?"
[Kenzo] Yeah. that's what I'm saying.
I'm saying don't worry about it.
We all see it. that. like.
when you're cuddling. I've never seen
that Bergie before. you know?
So. don't really overthink it.
I definitely respect my grandparents.
but at the same time.
they haven't even met Taylor in person.
I genuinely have feelings for Taylor.
and I wouldn't keep
pursuing this if I didn't.
We know what we have is true.
I think you guys are gonna
work it out outside of here.
Yeah. I think we are. too. It just sucked.
-Definitely sucks.
-You're good. Don't stress about it. bro.
You're good.
[narrator] Family means so much to me too.
Only the other day
I was on the phone to. um. ah.
you know. what's his name?
Big guy. quiet type.
Oh. it's on the tip of my tongue.
Oh. yeah. Dad.
It made me so happy to see you guys
react to seeing my family as well.
I just love them all with my entire heart.
I know you love your family
with your entire heart.
For sure.
-[phone chimes]
-Oh. fuck.
-Was that you or me?
-I got a text!
-[Taylor] What the fuck?
-What?
Are you serious right now?
-Who got a text?
-[Carmen] Who got a text?
[Taylor] We're all here. We're all here.
[sighs]
[Kyle] "Islanders.
the Hideaway is open tonight.
Please pick one couple
to spend the night alone together.
#DoNotDisturb. #LateNightSpecial."
[Bergie] Carmen and Kenzo!
Whoo!
Wait.
The boyfriend. girlfriend.
I think Kassy and Leo should go. Day ones.
[Kenzo] Me and Carmen.
I wanna respect Carmen's dad. um...
You know. he likes me.
so I don't wanna fuck that shit up. so...
-[Marco] Leo and Kassy. baby!
-Leo and Kassy!
[Kassy] Get me ready. I want my papi.
Ooh.
[Scott] What's going down tonight?
Mi hermano. Gracias.
-[Kenzo] I got you. bro. Love you.
-Gracias.
-Let's do it!
-[Johnnie] You ready to get ready?
I can't wait!
[Carmen] Yay!
[Leonardo] Damn. bro. I never thought
I would ever end up
in that fucking Hideaway.
-Well. you're going. buddy.
-[Leonardo] Can I just go in shorts?
-[Marco] No. you gotta go looking good.
-[Leonardo] Fuck.
All I know. bro. is I'm not putting on
those fucking nipple clamps.
-Well. put on something.
-[Bergie] Do everything.
I was like. "You know what?
We've had our little break.
We've had our distance.
I deserve a treat." you know?
-That's what I said.
-[Carmen] Yeah. you do.
What the heck?
I didn't expect this at all.
I was like. "Okay.
I'm not gonna say no.
Let's get it."
[Carmen] I think I like the pink.
-Very sexy.
-[Hannah] Yeah. it does.
Hell. no! [laughs]
[cheers]
[all laughing]
[Marco] That's a good fit. You look good.
I'm definitely excited.
Never thought I'd have the opportunity
to go inside of it. so...
That alone time with Kassy.
after everything we went through
and to get to where we are.
I feel like is much needed
and definitely much appreciated on my end.
Yes. baby!
Knowing that Leo's family is watching.
I'm gonna try and be more. um.
angelic tonight.
But I don't know about Leo.
He's more of a...
[Leonardo] All right.
Terrible.
Hello!
-Hello. Kassandra.
-You like? You like?
[Leonardo] I do. I look stupid as shit.
I love it.
-[Kassy] You look hilarious. [laughs]
-[Leonardo] You look delicious.
Okay. we're off!
[all cheering]
Bye!
[Leonardo] Oh. shit.
[Kassy] Oh. my gosh. this is so pretty.
-[Leonardo] Oh. shit!
-[Kassy] This is so cute!
[Leonardo] Okay. nah.
'Cause this is actually kind of fire.
[Leonardo] Come here. baby.
Ooh. Oh. that feels so good.
Oh. wow.
[Leo laughs]
You got it? Cheers to the Hideaway.
I know!
-Cheers.
-Cheers to you and me.
To you and me coming back together.
I can't even really begin to explain.
how you've been making me feel
the last couple of days
'cause I was really down.
and I'm just really happy that. like...
I got to show you
just little bits and pieces
of what you could expect in the future.
-Yeah.
-You know. 'cause in the future.
I'm not planning on stopping my gestures
and just showing you
my love for you all the time.
That's so sweet.
-Love you. baby.
-I love you too.
I did miss the three besos. I guess.
Yeah? I guess?
You sucked my lipstick off.
[narrator] The Hideaway has it all.
Champagne. flowers.
and the spa was
full of those little fishes
that nibble the dead skin off your feet.
Pure luxury.
Okay. everyone else. time for bed.
It's gonna be all right. brother.
It's gonna be all right.
Wait. what did he say was his exact words?
"The chemistry seems forced."
Whatever.
Most genuine connection I've had in here.
I am a sensitive person.
and. like.
I can't change that about myself.
That's just how I am.
[Destiny]
And you shouldn't... You shouldn't want to.
I said. "Kyle. you pursued me.
remember that."
I definitely got a lot of personality.
I give it that. but...
Nah. nah.
[Leonardo] What the fuck is this? [gasps]
Oh. hell. no.
That's giving. "I'm your pet."
And I ain't no pet.
[both laugh]
Ew. I don't like this shit. bro.
This looks mad fucking weird.
[Kassy] Playfulness. [giggles]
This is giving me the ick.
What is this for?
You ready to get fucking devoured?
Yeah. for sure.
Ooh. tickle. tickle.
Oh. my God. baby. you're so fucking sexy
the way you tickle me.
Said no man ever.
I love Grandma Donatelli.
She has no filter. though.
We gotta get her a filter.
She said. uh...
"Man. yeah. that's not a normal sleepover.
but it definitely was a porno."
[Hannah] She said it just like that. too.
[Bergie] Are you still feeling okay?
[Taylor] Yeah.
[Bergie] Yeah. I'm feeling okay.
[Taylor] Okay.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Leo and Kassy had a lovely time
in the Hideaway last night.
I'm not surprised.
Nothing says. "Sexy time"
quite like a wall-mounted
camera disguised as a dog.
Woof. woof.
[Leonardo] Good morning. baby.
How did you sleep?
[Kassy] I slept really good.
Let's go wake everyone else up.
In five minutes.
[Kassy laughs]
-[Leonardo] Let's go!
-[Kassy laughs]
[both] Good morning!
-We missed y'all.
-You look sleepy! You look sleepy!
[Leonardo] Ex-girlfriend.
-how you feeling?
-[Johnnie] Love you.
I miss my family so much.
-Let's have a good day.
I just wanna make my coffee.
I'm sorry. Carmen. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[Kassy] So cute.
I love it.
-I feel refreshed.
-I see the glow.
How'd you sleep. papa?
Oh. man. Slept solid. dawg.
-[Leonardo] Solid. solid.
-Slept good.
Hell. yeah.
[Kenzo] How was the Hideaway?
Like way more beautiful than I thought.
We had. like. glasses of champagne.
and it was just a good vibe.
We just were talking about how happy
we were to be here together.
And then. after we got into the bedroom.
and then we just started fucking around
with the toys in the closet.
But she fucking had me. like.
all the way chained up
and then put a blindfold over
just the eye socket part.
And then after that. you know.
did. uh. did some things.
Hit the grand salami.
-[Scott] Did you?
-Couple times.
Couple times? Jesus.
[laughs]
How was your night? Give us all the deets.
We went to the hot tub.
-There was candles everywhere.
-You had champagne?
Yes. we had champagne. chocolate. grapes.
And. you know. we...
[sighs] ...went to the bakery...
-[Taylor] Okay.
-...and...
we made a cake.
-We made three cakes.
-[Hannah screeches]
[all giggling]
[Taylor] Kassy. Kassy.
She said a triple layer.
[Taylor] You can call me mister.
Yeah. the Hideaway
was a lot of fun and hella romantic.
and she had on the most
fucking delicious set on.
Oh. my God.
I was barking like speed. bro.
So. yeah. all jokes aside.
it was definitely. like.
much more needed
than either of us thought.
But we had a great time.
-You deserve it. buddy.
-[Leonardo] Thank you. baby.
Hideaway was a lot of fun. um.
was everything we needed.
It was the cherry on top
to our full circle.
of. like. just our relationship
from the very beginning
to the end of us right now.
Knowing that I found Kassy...
Oh. my God. words can't even describe
how happy she really makes me.
and. um. I just can't wait to keep
showing her that in the real world.
So. it sounds like you'll
made the most of the Hideaway.
Yeah. we made the most of it.
And. yeah. we're just so excited to. like...
step out of here and keep doing us.
And thank y'all. thank y'all so much
for voting us in.
[Hannah] Of course. Kassy.
You guys deserve it.
[Johnnie] We love you.
We're so glad you had fun.
Triple-layer cake.
[narrator] Bergie was upset
by Grandpa Bergie's comments.
Grandpa can be very cutting.
I asked him what I could do
to make the show better.
and he said.
"Turn off your microphone."
[Hannah] Well. how are you feeling
about everything?
You could always. just vent.
lay it all out there.
I wasn't feeling too good about it
last night for sure. and this morning.
'Cause. like.
her mom said all these good things.
And then the only thing
that really stuck out last night
was what my grandpa said.
Everybody's like.
"Why does it look forced to him
and why is it like..."
I get it.
I think. allow yourself to feel.
-but then don't dwell on it.
-Yeah.
You know. too. the connection
that you have with Taylor.
-Yeah.
-And you have good instincts. Bergie.
You know if someone's genuine.
I think the ultimate thing on the outside
would just have to be
them meeting Taylor.
I have no idea
what they're actually thinking.
-Right.
-We're perceiving what they said.
-Don't be too in your head. okay?
-Okay.
-It happened.
-It's over. Let it go.
It's over.
Enjoy the time you still have with Taylor.
You got her mom's approval.
which is amazing
-'cause her mom's her everything.
-Yeah.
So. we got to think about the positives.
the wins.
Um. and then everything else on the
outside will sort itself out. I feel like.
Yeah.
[Bergie] If I had the chance
to talk to my grandparents.
I would have. like. expressed
how Taylor has been making me feel
in the Villa since I've been here.
Compared to everybody else.
she's the girl that has made me feel
the most confident and comfortable.
There's nothing we really can do
until we get out of here.
So. we're just gonna keep moving forward
like we have been in the past.
And then once we get out of here.
we'll take that step
of actually having a conversation
with our families.
-Okay?
-All right.
-I'm proud of you.
-Thank you.
You know. Bergie. I love you so much.
I would tell you if I saw anything forced.
if I saw anything.
and I just know that
she really cares about you.
And. um. we came in this together.
-We did.
-So. I'm very loyal.
So. I'm always gonna...
And just like you. for me.
you've always told me when you felt
something was wrong.
-What was off with Marco. Yeah.
-Uh-huh.
We should go to a movie
right when we get back.
-Like. the first night we're in LA?
-Mm-hmm.
-Whenever we land or whatever?
-Like a cute little movie theater.
-[gasps] Yeah.
-In Hollywood.
-Mmm.
-Yeah. I'm so excited.
And then we can do
Disney and Universal the next two.
-Mm-hmm.
-And then we can go to Solvang.
But...
how are we gonna get there?
-We might have to rent a car.
-Yeah.
And by we.
I mean you. Because I'm not old enough.
Let's do something fun today.
What do you think?
Um...
Okay.
Tickling my balls.
-No. Marco.
-You are.
Tickling my balls isn't fun.
-You are tickling them.
-Oh. okay.
I thought you said
let's do something fun today
like tickling my balls.
-[Marco] Jesus.
-[phone chimes]
-Oh. shit.
-Ooh.
I got a text!
-[Hannah] Yay!
-[Kassy gasps]
[Kyle groans]
"Islanders. it's time to get saucy
as you serve up some seriously
fast food in today's challenge.
Up N Down Diner. #NiceBuns.
#DoYouWantFriesWithThatShake."
[Leonardo] Mommy. turn off the TV right
now. You don't wanna see this shit.
But you know who's gonna be a pro at this?
Fucking Bergie.
General manager of Dairy Queen.
'Cause I know his ass was... [whooshing]
But who knows?
Maybe I'm gonna surprise myself.
[whooshes] You want a milkshake with that?
Let's have some fun! Yeah!
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
The final challenge of the season
is all about cooking.
and by coincidence.
playing it will be a baker's dozen...
minus one. So a dozen.
There's 12 of them is what I'm saying.
In today's challenge. Up-N-Down Diner...
Let's go. let's get cooking!
[narrator]...our couples will compete
against each other
to fulfill orders in the diner.
They'll need to make
a cheeseburger. loaded fries.
banana split. and a chocolate milkshake.
But each Islander
only has half the recipe.
so our couples must work together
to complete the item.
First to play is Kassy and Leonardo.
Destiny and Kyle. and Johnnie and Scott.
Each couple will sit
facing away from each other
with their wrists attached
to a pulley system.
[Islander] Make this food.
[whistle blows]
The bread!
Okay. I'm gonna get the bun.
I can't hear you! What's next?
Chili! Chili!
Oh. shit.
At first. we were trying to communicate.
-Kassy. what's next?
-[Kassy] Uh...
-[Hannah] Kassy!
-Kassy!
[Leonardo] All of those sorry
motherfuckers in the side
wanted to scream so much at us.
[Hannah screaming]
-Onion and pickles!
-What?
-[Destiny] Onions...
-Shut up! What?
I can't hear her trying to talk to me.
She can't hear me trying to talk to her.
Shout out. Kenzo.
Milk!
-[Kyle] What?
-[Kenzo] Milk!
Shut up!
Kyle! Here! Baby. your plate.
Ah! What the fuck?
[Scott] What's the one after banana?
-[Johnnie] Banana?
-[Scott] What's the one after banana?
[Johnnie] Add some more banana?
-Johnnie. what's the one after banana?
-[Johnnie] It's more banana!
I could not understand
anything with his accent.
I couldn't understand a thing
he was saying.
-Fries. fries. fries!
-Fries! Babe.
-[Leonardo] Oh. shit.
-Babe. the fries! The fries!
-[Leonardo] Hold on. hold on.
-[Kassy laughs]
[Kassy] Wait!
-[Taylor] Leo...
-[Bergie] Leo made his whole sandwich
and then decided
to throw the whole sandwich.
-[Kassy] Let me get the fries!
-[Leonardo] Fuck the fries!
[Kassy] Let me get the fries!
-[Kassy] Leo!
-[Leonardo] Fuck the fries!
-[Destiny] That's it!
-[Kyle] All right! Bell. hit the bell!
-[Kyle] Hit the bell!
-[Destiny] Milkshake! Come on! [groans]
Here we go! Very good! What's next?
-[Destiny] That's it!
-[Kyle] All right!
Of course. we can handle any type
of situation that is thrown at us.
Ain't that right?
Did you ever doubt it for a minute?
I didn't.
Hey!
Fuck. yeah!
But then I didn't realize that he threw
all the food he made at the end.
[Carmen] Leo. where's... Where's your food?
Oh. we're supposed to keep the food?
I am a good worker.
This guy got us fired.
Are you fucking serious?
-[Kassy] Leo.
-[Leonardo] Sorry.
[narrator] It's time for our remaining
couples to get involved.
Bergie and Taylor.
Hannah and Marco.
and Carmen and Kenzo.
To help Carmen and Kenzo
I pulled some strings.
But it just made things worse.
[screams] Marco! Fuck!
Marco. what the fuck?
I'm a pretty strong guy.
So. when I'm reaching. I feel bad
because I'm pulling on her shoulders.
And I'm sure it wasn't enjoying...
enjoyable for her.
[Hannah screams]
You are not letting me do anything.
Marco. she has no hands!
What do you mean she has no hands?
I can't do anything.
I think Marco forgot
that he was attached to Hannah.
'Cause he literally was just making his
meal. and Hannah...
-She wasn't doing shit.
-She's just like this.
Marco! What the fuck!
[Kassy] She gave up at that point.
She was just like...
What's after the beans?
[Bergie] Okay. you said onions. Onions.
-[Taylor] Onions?
-[Bergie] Yep. And...
I feel like I couldn't
do anything because. like.
he was pretty much
doing most of the meal making.
No!
[screams] Marco! Fuck!
Marco. what the fuck?
Kenzo! What are you doing?
My burger's done. babe!
-[Carmen] Babe. what...
-My burger is done!
In this challenge. he didn't even
give me the chance to use my arms.
-Are you done. babe?
-[Carmen] Yeah... [screams]
-Fuck.
-Carmen.
-[Johnnie] Kenzo!
-Are you done?
He sabotaged me.
Kenzo! I swear to God!
Fries!
[Kenzo] I couldn't hear.
And so. you know.
I just went about it my way.
-Here's the ketchup. babe!
-Are we done?
He literally was just dumping shit on me.
No. You just got cheese
in my fucking hair. We're break...
We're breaking up.
Bitch!
I think Kenzo's been
on a really strict diet.
so anytime he can venture off from that
he's gonna do some crazy crap.
-Whipped cream!
-[Carmen screams]
-Babe!
[Carmen] Are you kidding me!
Chocolate sauce!
No!
I hate this.
I have pickles on the fries!
[Bergie] Pickles! Pickles!
-Those are loaded fries.
-[Bergie] Those were some loaded fries.
I had everything in there.
I had the beans. I had the pickles.
I had the mayonnaise. I had the ketchup.
[Carmen] Put your arm down!
[Kyle] There we go. Mr. Dirty. baby!
-[Islander] Chocolate sauce!
-[Bergie] We're done we're done.
[bell rings]
[narrator] Well. if you've ever wondered
how many cooks it takes
to spoil the broth.
you have your answer.
Twelve will do it nicely.
Is it just me or do they look proud?
I think ours looks delicious.
What the fuck is that?
I'd like to say I made all four meals.
so I'm proud of myself.
-Give me that tip. you know?
-That's sick.
You know. I completed all four tasks here.
'Cause I'd eat it.
The burger. Oh. my God.
It's a vegan burger.
[Kyle] No meat...
[Destiny] No meat. no nothing
but lettuce and bun.
[Marco] Nice.
I love a milkshake that could
bring the boys to the yard.
So. I said leave it in the frickin pint.
-I have a banana.
-[Marco] That's terrible.
Then we got these loaded. um. chili fries.
They're pretty good.
[all] Ah!
-Kenzo!
-Oh. no!
The double milkshake!
Welcome to "Up-N-Down Dinner." baby!
I tried to make a Bergielicious meal.
and at 112 miles an hour.
-We got the iceberg milkshake.
-We got the iceberg.
That's what ten years of Dairy Queen does.
[narrator] These guys suck at cooking.
They really are cook suckers.
But the winners were Destiny and Kyle.
[cheering]
Eso!
[Kyle] We did the damn thing.
We won the final challenge of this season.
Big bragging rights. Okay?
That's the best flex.
Go ahead. Show 'em your muscle. Flex.
-I can't fl...
-Mm-hmm.
With all cheesy and everything.
we still come out on top. baby.
-[Kenzo] Food war!
-[Kassy] No. no. no!
[narrator] After that challenge.
Kyle was feeling the exact same way I did
after kissing a girl with braces
for the very first time.
It was gross. it was nasty.
but it was fun.
[Scott] Ah. I had a great laugh.
Me and him were going at it.
And it was fucking awesome. bro.
[Kassy] How do you feel about winning?
I feel great!
Everything is just crusted over on me.
I'm not made for this lifestyle.
I'm a very clean. aesthetic girly.
It was our last challenge too.
It was our last challenge. That's so sad.
-It was fun. though.
-It was fun.
[narrator]
Getting the messages from home earlier
have stirred up memories for Marco.
I was 21 when my mom passed. so...
It's about a year and a half now.
I lost her to liver failure.
Some life challenges hit her and...
she became an alcoholic.
Ended up getting deeper and deeper
into that addiction.
and I kind of lost her as my mother.
Today was hard.
To see everybody else's
family members in the videos.
you know. it was extremely hard.
Because she would have been
so proud of. you know.
the man that I became
throughout this process.
But she was definitely
watching from Heaven.
I don't like showing emotion to anybody.
Showing my heart makes me more vulnerable
to. you know.
get heartbroken and get hurt.
But I think she. honestly. sent me Hannah.
[Hannah] And remember that.
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
As the sun sets.
environmentally-aware couple.
Johnnie and Scott.
are sharing a shower to save water.
Oh. look. they're even sharing
their toothpaste.
Every little helps. guys.
I love you. baby.
It's going Britney Spears tonight. bitch.
Every couple in here is. like.
a couple I support and love.
Flashback. like. five weeks ago.
we didn't know what we were feeling.
Things were changing.
Love Island is Love Island-ing. for sure.
In regards to me and Destiny.
honestly. every conversation that we have.
I feel better and better about us.
Even though we went through
a million obstacles.
we separated. we got back together.
separated again.
I wouldn't. like. change the past
'cause then we wouldn't be
as strong as we are right now.
[Hannah] Let's have a good night.
-You okay?
-[Marco] You look hot.
[narrator] Destiny and Kyle won the food
challenge. I'm not surprised.
Their hamburger dipped in rancid cream.
trampled on.
then scraped off the filthy decking.
did look pretty appetizing.
This works.
How do you feel. winner?
-I feel good.
-[laughs]
I'm only two challenges deep.
-but I got a W under my belt.
-Okay.
-We got a W under our belt.
-We got the most important W.
The last W. You know what I'm saying?
-It feels good.
-Uh-huh.
-We winners.
-It was fun.
You really balance...
You balance me out.
Girl. I told you. I got you.
I told you I wasn't lying.
-I said I'm gonna hold it down.
-You right.
You held it down.
You did your thing. okay?
And it was... it was so fun.
Like. in that moment. I didn't think
about nothing else but having fun.
Everything happens for a reason.
you know what I'm saying?
There's a reason we're still here. So...
We keep on rolling. We keep on moving.
Mama threw a little curveball.
But it's okay. we gonna get to her.
-You can still hit a curveball.
-We gonna hit New York.
You could still hit a curveball
out of the park.
-You know what I'm saying?
-You can.
-How do you feel?
-[Scott] How do I feel?
About tonight. if we were to be...
sent home tonight?
I didn't really expect to find
a connection. if I'm being honest.
And this has caught me by surprise.
So. whatever we have to do
to make this work.
I'm up for it.
So. do you feel confident
with where we are if we left today?
-Yeah.
-I was hopeful
to find a connection in here.
I really was.
And. literally. when you came in.
it was a bombshell.
So I'll just start playing
eye-contact games.
-Playing eye-contact games?
-Yeah.
-Which always works.
What are you laughing at?
-Nothing.
-What are you laughing for?
'Cause every time I look at you.
you're like...
This is just my normal look.
It just seems intense.
How are you feeling
after last night and everything?
-Feeling better.
-Better?
Just having time to think about it
and. like. process it. But...
[Taylor] Yeah.
You know what's crazy. though?
It's like things are going. like.
-so good between us...
-Yeah.
...that I get scared.
when we get out of here.
Yeah.
[stammers] But we've talked about.
just take it day by day.
-I know. but I. like...
-Yeah.
I don't... I just want you to know I...
I don't think you know
how much I like you.
[stammers] I probably don't
even make it known
because I'm afraid of getting hurt.
-if that makes sense.
-That makes sense.
[Taylor] Do you feel the same way?
I'm just thinking. I also do feel like
I'm holding back
just 'cause the distance thing
is in the back of my mind.
-Yeah.
-I'm just not letting myself...
-fully into it right now just 'cause...
-Yeah.
I wanna see how things work
with long distance
and I don't wanna get hurt.
-It's kind of my big fear right now.
-Yeah.
I get it.
They need to build compatibility.
-You're right.
-The chemistry doesn't seem there.
[Hannah] He said that?
No. I just take it as
Grandpa's words. probably.
Oh.
I like to be as real as possible
and. like. focus on the reality.
And if the reality is
you really see an issue with the distance.
then I don't wanna keep
indulging in a relationship
if that's a huge concern
that you're not really
willing to take. like. a risk.
If that's not a risk
you're willing to take.
Like. it's not fair to me.
Yeah. I understand that.
[Taylor] I live in Dallas. Texas.
He's Midwest.
so I'm really not seeing
distance as an issue.
For me to hear that
distance is still on his mind
and it is an issue for him...
just has me a little concerned.
Okay.
If it does have anything
to do with the videos.
then I would hope that. you know.
he feels like he can address that to me.
[Hannah] Where did she go?
Come to the fire. Bergie.
-Let me sit up. babe.
-[Marco] Hurry up.
-[Bergie] I don't know what's going on.
-[Marco] What?
[Bergie] Like. we were just talking.
She feels like she doesn't express
how much she cares about me
'cause she's scared of getting hurt
and then I said the same thing
'cause I'm scared of getting hurt
from the long-distance thing.
And then how she ended that was like.
"Well. if you don't think
you can do long distance..."
-[Hannah] Oh. God.
-"...we shouldn't have to make this work."
And then I didn't know what to say
after that.
-How do you feel?
-Not good. Obviously.
-[Marco] Yeah. how could you feel good?
-I care for her.
And I feel terrible right now.
And I want it to work.
It's not like I don't want it to work.
But here's what I feel.
I feel like you were just being honest.
okay?
And that's truly how I'm feeling.
Exactly. And it's not a negative thing.
It's just how you're feeling.
It's how you feel that you honestly
can't give everything right now
because you're nervous about it.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I don't see anything wrong with that.
I think it's good
that you're being transparent.
[Bergie] I really just don't
wanna get hurt. I've been hurt.
-Yeah. you've been hurt too many times.
-Now I'm hurting again.
This feels like shit.
[Bergie] You wanna go to All The Feels?
-[Taylor] Yeah.
-[Bergie] Okay.
-[Bergie] How are you doing?
-I'm good. Uh...
-Do you want to go to All The Feels?
-Yeah. let's go to All The Feels.
[Taylor] Sorry I walked off like that.
[Bergie] You're good.
I definitely just wanna clear that out.
[narrator] It's getting late. and the
Islanders might be having some downtime.
but emotions are about to run high...
land. Yes!
Sarah Hyland is in the Villa.
-[Taylor] Oh. shit.
-[Bergie] Ah. shit.
Hi. Islanders.
Hi. Sarah.
[all] Oh!
[Marco] Hey. Sarah!
[Leonardo] What up. Sarah?
Hello!
Can you all please
join me by the fire pit?
[sighs]
Islanders.
I have some very important news.
America has been voting
for the couples that they want to see
in the Love Island finale.
The four couples
who received the most votes
will go through to the finale.
The two couples with the fewest votes
will be dumped from the island
tonight.
Please. stand up.
In no particular order.
I can now reveal
that the first couple saved by the public
and through to the Love Island finale is...
Carmen and Kenzo.
The second couple
America wants to see in the finale is...
Hannah and Marco.
The third couple safe is...
Kassy and Leo.
So.
three couples remain.
Johnnie and Scott.
Taylor and Bergie.
and Destiny and Kyle.
Only one more couple
is going through
to the Love Island finale.
The other two couples...
will be going home
tonight.
The last couple through
to the Love Island finale...
is...
[narrator]
Welcome back to Love Island USA.
Just one place remains
in the Love Island finale.
But who has America chosen to fill it?
Johnnie and Scott.
Bergie and Taylor.
or Destiny and Kyle?
The last couple through
to the Love Island finale
is...
Taylor and Bergie.
Well done. Take a seat.
Destiny. Kyle.
Johnnie and Scott.
unfortunately.
your time on the island
has come to an end.
Johnnie and Scott. how are you feeling?
Coming here. not really expecting too much
to find a connection
but I was always open to it.
and I feel like I have.
So. I wanna wish you all the best.
I'm just so happy that I met you guys
and I'm so happy for you guys.
I genuinely feel like you guys
all can make it outside of here.
I feel like you guys
all have such a deep connection
that I look up to in a lot of ways.
So. I'm gonna be. you know.
rooting for you guys on the outside.
And I love you guys.
[Hannah] We love you. Johnnie.
Destiny and Kyle. how are you feeling?
Um. obviously. it's bittersweet.
but honestly. I feel...
I feel fricking great. to be honest.
Got a good-looking woman by my side.
So. you know. I really have no complaints.
Destiny.
you have been here since day one.
How are you feeling?
It's been a pleasure and an honor.
What I always say. it's not goodbye.
it's. "I will see all of y'all later."
[Marco] One more thing. one more thing.
Destiny will be destiny.
Destiny will be destiny. okay?
The icon.
You silly.
[Sarah] Well. Destiny. Kyle.
Johnnie and Scott.
I will leave you to say your good-byes.
The rest of you.
congratulations.
You are our Love Island finalists.
I will see you all very soon.
Bye for now.
-[Leonardo] Bye. Sarah.
-[all] Bye!
[Sarah] Bye.
-[Scott] Nice to meet you.
-[Marco] Nice to meet you.
Johnnie!
-I just love you so much.
-[Carmen] I love you so much more.
[Destiny] I'm not doing this with y'all.
No. no. [laughs]
No good-byes. No. we don't.
[Marco] Give me a goodbye.
Give me a goodbye.
[Destiny] You the only one that get it.
-[Kenzo] My dawg. Thanks a lot.
-[Kyle] My dawg. bro.
-The last Casa person standing.
-I know.
[Scott] You too. mate. You too.
We had a lot of damn lives.
-We had a great...
-[Leonardo] And crazy moments.
-It stays with us a lifetime.
-[Leonardo] Yeah.
-[Bergie] What a pleasure. man.
-Have a good one. mate.
-Scott from Wales. [laughs]
-Kassandra.
Marco! [shouts]
[Taylor] I'm so happy.
[Bergie] We've been through so much shit.
[Destiny] I need you to carry it
to the end for me.
-Well. we made... [stammers]
-[Destiny] We made it this far.
[Bergie] Yeah. we made it this far.
Destiny. she's somebody
I've known since day one.
It was just me and her
as the last day-one girls.
I'm so proud of her.
And I'm happy now that she has Kyle.
I see a good connection
forming outside of this.
and I hope that they continue it.
[Leonardo]
It's gonna be the emptiest of the empty.
-Life outside...
-Is crazy.
[Johnnie] If I left by myself.
I was leaving content.
it would be cool. but I leave with a man!
[Hannah] Oh. Destiny. Oh. Johnnie.
[Johnnie]
All right. Check your guys' closets.
[Kassy] Will do. [giggles]
[Johnnie] 'Cause I was a community closet.
[Leonardo] How about fucking Kyle
holding it down?
Only Casa boy out here thugging it out
to literally the very end.
You made it. You know what I mean?
Hell. yeah!
[Leonardo]
Kyle. you doing good over there?
Yeah. baby. I'm good.
[Taylor] Cute.
Yay!
Johnnie...
became my best friend in here overnight.
So. I'm gonna miss her like crazy.
but it's not goodbye.
it's a "see you soon."
And then. obviously.
with Scott. I'm just happy
that he's here to make my girl
Johnnie happy.
I really wish them nothing but the best.
[Leonardo] Love you. girl.
[Kyle] I'm rooting for every one
of you guys.
So. kill it. have fun.
and enjoy the rest of your time.
We love y'all.
Bye. Johnnie! Bye. Scott!
Bye. Johnnie. Bye!
[all cheering]
-I love you!
-Bye! We love y'all!
Leaving together feels like we're leaving
because it's like I came in here
to find a person. my person.
and I feel like I made
such a great connection.
and we'll see where it goes.
[Scott] My time in the villa...
Short. sweet. but worthwhile.
I'm excited to see how
the connection with this one goes.
I like being around her.
[Destiny] You don't always find your
person immediately in life.
and that's totally okay.
But it matters how you pick up
and keep going.
I kept going
and here I am.
[Kyle] I feel like every couple in there
truly deserves it.
And leaving here with
a fine little chocolate-thing
next to me. I feel good.
No complaints over here.
[Kassy] Girls. are we going
to the bakery tonight?
Wow. That's how she worded it?
-[Leonardo] The fucking bakery?
-They not baking a cake.
you just caught on to that?
What does baking cake mean?
It's girl code for
the steps of a relationship here.
It's like bases. Except with baking.
Yeah. Sexual.
-What base are we at?
-[phone chimes]
-Oh. hey!
-I got a text!
-[all cheer]
-[Bergie] Let's go.
"Islanders. congratulations
on making it to the finale
of Love Island USA 2023.
#FinalFour. #CoupleGoals."
[cheering]
Final four...
[Marco] We'll do a cheers.
We'll do a cheers.
-A group cheers. Group cheers.
-[Hannah] Yeah. group cheers.
Group cheers.
Hey!
[Marco]
Thrilled to make the finals. obviously.
I found exactly what I came here for.
times a thousand and beyond.
I wanna fucking win.
Shit. We're here. Fuck it. Right?
I already won her. I already won
our connection. I already our love.
You know. it's time to win it all.
Just kiss me!
Cheers to making it this far.
finding our person.
and the Love Island finale.
[cheering]
I definitely found what I came here for.
We're good to go now.
Like. we've been good to go.
Salud.
[Leonardo] If you're truly in love
with somebody. go hard for them.
There isn't anything I wouldn't do
for this girl next to me.
[Kassy] Like I said. we're magnets.
-Magnets.
-We can't be separated.
-Yeah. we can't be separated.
-Literally.
Congratulations. guys.
Congratulations. everyone.
I couldn't be happier right now.
I couldn't be happier either.
[Leonardo] Let's go.
Yeah.
-[Marco] Finals!
-Yeah!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm